INDRA BAHADUR PUN

Mobile: 0432883211

Email: indrapun21@gmail.com

Address: 4/90 Copeland Street, Liverpool, NSW 2170 **LinkedIn:** www.linkedin.com/in/indra-bahadur-pun

GitHub: https://github.com/endra7

CAREER OBJECTIVE

With a Master of Technology degree in Enterprise Systems and Business Analytics and a Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science and Engineering, I wish to work in an analyst job profile in a challenging work environment in coordination with team members to analyse and develop business or information technology-related solutions. If given the opportunity, I would like to lead and oversee the realisation of potential opportunities into the strengths of the organisation within the next five years.

KEY STRENGTHS

- Fast Learner and Adaptable: Ability to produce quality results under short training periods allowed my current employers to deploy me into various job roles as required by the organisation.
- Leadership and Team Player: As a team leader, my team completed a major project with the highest possible grades because of the well-planned execution of project management processes and strong team-building practices.
- Multi-lingual: I am proficient in English, Nepali and Hindi.
- **Time Management:** I was able to maintain work-study balance by efficiently utilising my time to earn my livelihood as well as to maintain exceptional academic records.
- **Problem Solver and Innovative:** As a student mentor, I was able to provide ideas to my mentees to uniquely approach various projects and assignments while remaining within the university's assignment requirements and guidelines.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

Professional Year Program (Information Technology)

Feb 2020 – Current

Queensland International Business Academy, Sydney Campus

A career development program to enhance student's employability by combining formal learning and Australian workplace experience.

Master of Technology (Enterprise Systems and Business Analytics) International Institute of Business and Information Technology Federation University Mar 2018 - Nov 2019

Enterprise Systems	High Distinction	Grade Point
Business Process Analytics and Change	High Distinction	6.93/7.0
Real-Time Analytics	High Distinction	0.93/7.0

Bachelor of Technology (Computer Science and Engineering) NIMS (National Institute of Medical Sciences) University, India

May 2013 - May 2017

Programming	Distinction	Aggragata
Database Management Systems	Distinction	Aggregate
Data Mining and Warehousing	Distinction	Percentage of 82.84%
Software Project Management	Distinction	02.04%

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

Title: Build a Web Application for a Retail Supermarket Chain.

Aug 2019 - Oct 2019

Objective: To develop and document "Human Resource Planning and Shift Management Solution" for a supermarket client.

Tools: Bootstrap 4.0, PHP, MySQL, jQuery, GitHub, Google docs, Apache Web Server

Duties:

With the role as a Project Manager and Product Owner for 'Master Project', my team used the agile scrum methodology to successfully execute the 'Master Project' to develop the 'HR Planning and Shift Management System' within the allocated time constraint. I, along with my three other team members, developed in-built, interactive and richly visualized dashboards for the analytical report from the shift data collected through our developed web application from the supermarket's employees.

Outcome: The project exceeded the external client's requirements, resulting in a highly satisfied client. The documentation and demonstration resulted in 'High Distinction'.

Title: Prepare Data Analytics Report for Airbnb.

Mar 2019 - May 2019

Objective: To analyse publicly accessible datasets to prepare data analytics report and provide recommendation for Airbnb to enhance the guest experience.

Tools: SAP Predictive Analytics, SAP Lumira, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Word

Duties:

With the help of the analytical tools, I prepared an analytical report to recommend restructuring of the Airbnb's property listing operations as well as introducing a new advertisement strategy for enhancing the guest experience whilst improving the revenue of the organisation.

Outcome: The detailed analytical report resulted in 'High Distinction'.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Batching / Filler / Packaging Operator Freedom Foods Group Limited

Mar 2018 - Current

Duties and Responsibilities:

Duties and Responsibilities:

- Adhere to quality guidelines of the dairy products.
- Adhere to Good Manufacturing Practices.
- Follow the Work Health and Safety instructions and document potential hazards in the workplace.
- Escalate any issues related to operational performances or quality of products through the chain of command.
- Document any abnormalities in machine performances and the quality of products.

Student Mentor Aug 2019 – Nov 2019 International Institute of Business and Information Technology

international institute of dusiness and infor

- Train students to the university's assignment guidelines and requirements.
- Encourage and guide students to solve assignments and projects.
- Encourage students to actively participate in the mentoring sessions.
- Provide feedback of students to the Academic Coordinator.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

	Years Exp.	Last Used	Ability out of 10 (High = 10)
Development languages			
C / C++	2 Years	2017	6
PHP	3 months	2019	7
Java	6 months	2014	5
Python	2 years	2020	7
Web technologies & protocols			
HTML	3 years	2020	8
JavaScript	2 years	2020	6
CSS	3 years	2020	7
XML	3 years	2015	5
JSON	2 years	2020	7
13014	2 years	2020	/
IDE's/Tools			
Microsoft Visual Studio	4 years	2020	7
Eclipse	3 months	2016	5
Anaconda Navigator	6 months	2020	7
Android Studio	3 months	2017	6
Github	5 months	2020	7
Databases			
MySQL	2 years	2019	8
Firebase	4 months	2017	6
Analytical Tools			
SPSS	3 months	2019	7
Microsoft Excel	3 years	2019	7
SAP Lumira	4 months	2019	7
SAP Predictive Analytics	4 months	2019	7
574 Fredictive Finally ties	4 1110111113	2013	,
Operating Systems			
Linux	2 years	2016	5
Windows	6 Years	2020	8
Frameworks			
React.js	3 months	2020	6
Bootstrap 4.0	3 months	2019	7
υσοιστιαρ 4.0	2 1110111115	2013	ļ ,

ACHIEVEMENTS/AWARDS

- i. Awarded 'Merit Scholarship' because of my academic excellence.
- ii. Awarded 'First Position' in the university examinations.

PROFESSIONAL AFFILIATIONS

Australian Computer Society: ACS Membership Number 4179019 Joined: Jan 2020

Golden Key International Honour Society: GK ID: 9000832241

Golden Key International Honour Society is an academic honour society which recognizes scholastic achievement and excellence among university students. Membership is by invitation only.

Joined: Apr 2019

REFERENCES

Dr Monica Jan
Lecturer
Federation University
Contact information to be provided upon request

Mr Alan Lwin General/Operations Manager Freedom Foods Group Limited, Ingleburn Contact information to be provided upon request